budk.com 2019-11-26

# Privacy

Updated: February 21, 2018 

###  Scope of this Online Privacy Statement

This Online Privacy Statement describes how BUDK.com uses, shares and protects the personal information we collect through BUDK.com. “Personal information” is information that identifies you personally, either alone or in combination with other information. Personal information may include, for example, your name, address, email address, credit card information, and transaction history. 

### Your Email Privacy

BUDK.com values and respects your online privacy. Although we collect and save your email address in order to share information with you about your order, if you do not wish to receive emails from us, we will remove you from our list as soon as possible. BUDK.com is a division of BUDK, and BUDK does not sell, rent, or distribute your email address to anyone. 

### Your Consent to This Online Privacy Statement

By browsing or using BUDK.com, you are agreeing to the collection, use, and disclosure of information related to your purchase as described in this Online Privacy Statement. 

Questions Concerning Our Online Privacy Practices 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Online Privacy Statement or our privacy practices, please email us at webcs@budk.com or write to us at BUDK Catalog, PO Box 2768, Moultrie, GA 31776. 

### Privacy Notices

This Online Privacy Statement may be supplemented or amended from time to time by “privacy notices” posted on this site. For example, certain pages of this site contain privacy notices providing details about the ways we use or share the personal information we collect on those pages. 

### This Online Privacy Statement May Change

We reserve the right to update or modify this Online Privacy Statement, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version on this site. These changes will only apply to personal information we collect after we have posted the revised Online Privacy Statement on this site. Your use of this site following any such change constitutes your agreement that all personal information collected from or about you through BUDK.com after the revised Online Privacy Statement is posted will be subject to the terms of the revised Online Privacy Statement. To alert you to changes to this Online Privacy Statement, we will provide a notice at the top of this Online Privacy Statement for at least 30 days after the new effective date of such changes and highlight the changes so that you can locate them easily. 

You may access the current version of this Online Privacy Statement at any time by clicking on the link marked "Privacy Statement" at the bottom of each page of this site. 

## What Personal Information Do We Collect on BUDK.com?

### Information You Give Us

We collect the personal information you knowingly and voluntarily provide when you use BUDK.com, for example, the information you provide when you register, sign-in, search, purchase products, submit product reviews, sign up for our e-mail newsletters, or communicate with customer service. Depending on how you use this site, you may supply us with information such as your name, address, phone number, email address, or credit card information, or information about people to whom purchases will be shipped (for example, a gift recipient). 

### Information Sent to Us by Your Web Browser

We collect information that is sent to us by your Web browser, such as your IP address, the address of the Web page you were visiting when you accessed Shop BUDK.com, the date and time of your visit, and information about your computer’s operating system. Please check your browser if you want to learn what information your browser sends or how to change your settings. The information provided by your browser does not identify you personally. We use this non-personal information primarily to create statistics that help us improve this site and make it more compatible with the technology used by our visitors. However, if you have created a user identity on one of your visits to this site or if you access this site by clicking on a link in an email we have sent you, we may combine the information provided by your browser to information that identifies you personally. 

### Information We Collect Using Cookies and Other Web Technologies

We use "cookies" and other Web technologies to collect information and support certain features of this site. For example, we use these technologies to collect information about the ways visitors use our site – which pages they visit, which links they use, and how long they stay on each page. Cookies and other Web technologies are also used to support the features and functionality of our site — for example, to track the contents of your shopping cart as you move from page to page. These technologies also permit us to keep a record of your previous choices and preferences so that we can personalize your shopping experience and save you the trouble of reentering information already in our database. Generally, the information we collect using these Web technologies does not identify you personally, however, it may be linked to information that does identify you personally, such as the information you provide when you make a purchase or register to use a special feature of our site. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. You may also delete our cookies as soon as you leave BUDK.com. Although you are not required to accept our cookies when you visit BUDK.com, if you set your browser to reject cookies, you will not be able to use all of the features and functionality of this site. 

### Information We Collect From Other Sources

We may supplement the information collected through this site with information we collect in other ways. For example, if you call our toll-free number, we may collect your telephone number and add it to our database. We may also supplement the information collected through this site with information from third parties, including data brokers. By supplementing your profile with information from other sources, we are better able to provide product recommendations and special offers that will be of genuine interest to you. We may also use this additional information to further personalize our site and improve your shopping experience. 

### Use of Cookies and Similar Technologies by Our Advertising Agents

BUDK.com uses third-party advertising companies to place online advertisements on our behalf at websites other than BUDK.com. These advertising companies may use cookies and Web beacons (also known as “pixel tags”) to target and measure the effectiveness of their advertisements. For example, our advertising companies may place Web beacons on their clients’ Web sites. When you visit these Web sites, the Web beacon “tags” your computer with a “cookie” that collects and stores information about your visit to their client’s Web site. This information does not identify you personally. Our advertising companies use the information they collect about your use of their clients’ Web sites to customize the advertisements you see when you visit their clients’ Web sites. Our advertising companies’ use of cookies and Web beacons is covered by their privacy policies, not by this Online Privacy Statement. 

### First Party Cookie Integration

We may also use technologies, such as our own cookies, to provide you with relevant online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of our cookies used for this online advertising, [click here.](http://dtmc.budk.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=62685&cname=BUDK&cmagic=24270e&clogo=62685.png&loc=us&lang=en-us)

### How Do We Use Your Personal Information?

We may use the personal information we collect through BUDK.com:   

  * to fulfill your order for BUDK.com products or services;
  * to provide you with the information, products and services you request or purchase;
  * for security, credit or fraud prevention purposes;
  * to provide you with effective customer service;
  * to provide you with a personalized shopping experience;
  * to display personalized advertising when you visit this site;
  * to contact you with special offers and other information we believe will be of interest to you;
  * to contact you with information and notices related to your use of this site or your purchases;
  * to invite you to participate in surveys and provide feedback to us;
  * to better understand the your needs and interests;
  * to improve the content, functionality and usability of this site;
  * to improve our products and services;
  * to improve our marketing and promotional efforts; and
  * for any other purpose we identify in a specific privacy notice.

### With Whom Do We Share the Personal Information We Collect Through BUDK.com?

We may share the personal information we collect through this site as described below and in any applicable privacy notices. 

### Our Corporate Affiliates

We may share your personal information with our subsidiaries and parent and sister corporations (our “corporate affiliates”), who may use this information to contact you with information and offers they believe will be of interest to you. The corporate affiliates’ use of your personal information shall be subject to this Online Privacy Statement. 

### Other Business Partners and Selected Vendors

We work closely with certain business partners and carefully selected vendors to provide you with access to their product offerings. We may share personally identifiable information about you with these business partners or selected vendors, and they may use this information to offer you products and/or services that they believe will be of interest to you. 

We may from time to time contract with third party vendors to provide ads to our customers on behalf via the Internet or to send direct mail or catalogs to customers whom we think may be interested in our products or services. In order to do so, such vendor may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website using a “cookie”. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser or mobile device by websites, mobile apps, and advertisements that you access or use. This data is stored on your browser or mobile device and helps website and mobile apps to remember things about you to improve your experience with the website. Third-party vendors may then pool the anonymous information that they collect from our website with other sources of information, which may include your name and mailing address, for purposes of determining whether you might be interested in receiving direct mail or a catalog. If you do not wish for cookies to be placed on your computer, most web browsers permit you to prevent that from taking place. However, please keep in mind that these technologies are an important part of how the website works; removing, rejecting or limiting the use of cookies or other similar technologies might affect the availability and functionality of the website. To opt-out of receiving our direct mail or catalogs, you may send us an email at [webcs@budk.com](mailto:webcs@budk.com) or call us at 1-800-630-2835. 

### Government and Legal Disclosures

We may disclose the personal information we collect through BUDK.com when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law (or a court order or subpoena); to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to enforce the Terms of Use or other agreements that govern your use of this site; to protect the rights, property or safety of BUDK.com, our users or others; or to protect your vital interests. 

### What Choices Do You Have?

BUDK.com respects your right to make choices about the ways we collect, use and disclose your personal information. We generally ask you to indicate your choices at the time that you register as a user of BUDK.com or the time and on the page where you provide your personal information. You may browse BUDK.com without providing any information that identifies you personally and may choose not to provide the information we request, although this may mean that you cannot make a purchase or take advantage of other BUDK.com features. We may periodically send you information and product promotions via e-mail. You may “opt-out” of receiving our promotional e-mails at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of the particular newsletter or e-mail. You may also manage your subscription and email preferences by clicking on “My Account” on BUDK.com or by sending us an email at webcs@budk.com. 

### Security

BUDK.com has industry standard measures in place to protect the security of the personal information we collect through BUDK.com. For example, we use Secure Socket Layers (“SSL”) to encrypt your credit card information as it travels over the Internet. It is important that you understand, however, that no Web site or database is completely secure or “hacker proof.” You are also responsible for taking reasonable steps to protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure or misuse, for example, by protecting your passwords. 

### Children and Minors

BUDK.com is not directed at nor targeted to children We do not use this site to knowingly solicit personal information from or market to children. If you are under 18 years of age, you should not submit any personal information to us. 

Updated: February 21, 2018
